Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Slover, Ina W. (Box 72)
  - Slums (Box 72)
  - Smallwood, Donald L. (Box 72)
  - Smart, Ms. Tina M. (Box 72)
  - Smiley, George (Box 72)
  - Smitch, George (Box 72)
  - Smith, Anne (Box 72)
  - Smith, Becky (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mrs. Beverly (Box 72)
  - Smith, Carrye (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. China B. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Miss Cindy (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. Clay T. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Ms. D. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Dan C. (Box 72)
  - Smith, D. H. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Dick (Box 72)
  - Smith, E. L. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Euella (Box 72)
  - Smith, Floyd (Box 72)
  - Smith, Frances R. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Glen D. (Box 72)
  - Smith, M. K. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. Howard (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mrs. Jack (Box 72)
  - Smith, James A. (Box 72)
  - Smith, James C. Jr. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. James K. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Jess W. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Ms. Joyce (Box 72)
  - Smith, Dr. Lamar E. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mrs. Marie S. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Ms. Marsha (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mike (Box 72)
  - Smith, Nancy Jo (Box 72)
  - Smith, Nancy O. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Pam (Box 72)
  - Smith, Paul W. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Gov. & Mrs. Preston (File 2) (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. Price (Box 72)
  - Smith, Rev. Ralph M. (Box 72)
  - Smith, Mr. Sidney C. (Box 72)
  - Snelson, Mr. & Mrs. Pete (Box 72)
  - Snodgrass, Mr. & Mrs. Weldon (Box 72)
  - Snooks, Mrs. Kay (Box 72)
  - Snow, Ron (Box 72)
  - Snyder, Bill (Box 72)
  - Snyder, Mr. James L. (Box 72)
  - Snyder, John (Box 72)
  - Snyder, Ken (Box 72)
  - Sobczak, James (Box 72)
  - Sobol, Richard (Box 72)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers (Box 72)
  - Social Workers (Box 72)
  - Somerville, Mr. & Mrs. Wayne (Box 72)
  - Southerland, Mrs. Cliff (Box 72)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (Box 72)
  - Southern Forest Institute, Inc. (Box 72)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board (Box 72)
  - Southern Interstate Nuclear Board (Box 72)
  - Southern Legislative Conference (Box 72)
  - Southside Girls Club (Box 72)
  - South Texas University System (Box 72)
  - Southwest Research Institute (Box 72)
  - Southwestern Life Inc. Co. (Box 72)
  - San Antonio River Authority (Box 73)
  - Sanchez, Mr. & Mrs. Henry (Box 73)
  - Sanders, G. E. (Box 73)
  - Sanders, H. W. (Box 73)
  - Sanderson, Mrs. M. L. (Box 73)
  - San Francisco, California (Box 73)
  - Schuler, Miss Helen (Box 73)
  - Sabina, Sister M. R. N. (Box 73)
  - Sadberry, Mr. & Mrs. A. M. (Box 73)
  - Sadler, Jerry (Box 73)
  - Saint Mark's Methodist Church (Box 73)
  - Saint Stephen's Episcopal Church (Box 73)
  - Salcines, Mr. E. J. (Box 73)
  - Sales Tax (Box 73)
  - Salter, Bob (Box 73)
  - Salter, Joe (Box 73)
  - Samford, Emma Lee (Box 73)
  - Sammons, Mrs. Dorothy (Box 73)
  - San Angelo (Box 73)
  - Santiesteban, Mr. & Mrs. Tati (Box 73)
  - Sargent, Earl (Box 73)
  - Sarofim, Mrs. Fayes (Box 73)
  - Satin, Joseph (Box 73)
  - Satterwhite, M. D. (Box 73)
  - Savage, Jerri (Box 73)
  - Sawdy, Gordon F. (Box 73)
  - Savings Bank Life Insurance (Box 73)
  - Sawyer, Mr. & Mrs. Bill (Box 73)
  - Sawyer, Drew Grant (Box 73)
  - Scabee, Mrs. (Box 73)
  - Sealing, Mr. & Mrs. Harry (Box 73)
  - Scarlott, Mackie C. (Box 73)
  - Schaefer, Walter W. (Box 73)
  - Schaffner, Gerta (Box 73)
  - Schanlaub, Orvel W. (Box 73)
  - Schellhase, Merl B. (Box 73)
  - Schenk, Cletus C. (Box 73)
  - Scheurer, R. S. (Box 73)
  - Schiller, Rep. & Mrs. Milton (Box 73)
  - Schlitz Brewing Co. (Box 73)
  - Schlump, Mrs. Mamie (Box 73)
  - Schmidt, Mrs. Robert E. (Box 73)
  - Sehnabel, Charles A. (Box 73)
  - Schneider, Mrs. Ernest (Box 73)
  - Schneider, Mary S. (Box 73)
  - Schools (Box 73)
  - School Books (Box 73)
  - School Buses (Box 73)
  - School Districts (Box 73)
  - Schroeder, Mrs. Anna M. (Box 73)
  - Scofield, Mrs. J. A. (Box 73)
  - Schwoerke, Mr. Lewis H. (Box 73)
  - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe) (Box 73)
  - Scofield, Maude (Box 73)
  - Scoggin, G. F. (Box 73)
  - Scott, Annie (Box 73)
  - Scott, Mrs. Evelyn (Box 73)
  - Scott, Mrs. Lelia Crain (Box 73)
  - Scott, Mrs. M. F. (Box 73)
  - Scott, W. B. (Box 73)
  - Scott, Wallace H. Jr. (Box 73)
  - Scouting (Box 73)
  - Schmitt, C. C. (Box 73)
  - Schroeder, Mr. Raymond (Box 73)
  - Scroggins, Paul (Box 73)
  - Seale, Nell (Box 73)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co. (Box 73)
  - Securities Board (Box 73)
  - Secret Service (Box 73)
  - Seddleman, Jan (Box 73)
  - Seddon, Mr. John (Box 73)
  - Segers, Mrs. Jean (Box 73)
  - Seidel, Raymond L. (Box 73)
  - Seitz, Buster (Box 73)
  - Seitz, Nick (Box 73)
  - Selby, Ms. Sue (Box 73)
  - Sells, Mr. & Mrs. Magellan (Box 73)
  - Selph, Mrs. Bertha (Box 73)
  - Semos, Mr. & Mrs. Chris (Box 73)
  - Senate (Box 73)
  - Senatorial District (Box 73)
  - Senior Citizens Service of North Texas, inc. (Box 73)
  - Senn, Mr. Kenneth (Box 73)
  - Servies, Mrs. Ronald G. (Box 73)
  - Sertoma Club (Box 73)
  - Sewer (Box 73)
  - Sex Education (Box 73)
  - Seventh Day Adventists (Box 73)
  - Shaddock, Mr. Joe E. (Box 73)
  - Shaffer, Kirk (Box 73)
  - Sewage (Box 73)
  - Shack, Bruce (Box 73)
  - Shaffer, Mrs. Eula Mae (Box 73)
  - Shahan, Mr. & Mrs. Happy (Box 73)
  - Shannon, Tommy (Box 73)
  - Sharp, Mr. Bill (Box 73)
  - Shaw, Carmon (Box 73)
  - Shaw, Mrs. E. M. (Box 73)
  - Shaw, S. L. (Box 73)
  - Shearn Moody Interests (Box 73)
  - Shears, Ms. Ester (Box 73)
  - Shell Oil Company (Box 73)
  - Shelton, Bill R. (Box 73)
  - Sheppard Air Force Base (Box 73)
  - Sheppard Civilian Credit Union (Box 73)
  - Sheppard Federal Credit Union (Box 73)
  - Sheppard, Mrs. Beatrice (Box 73)
  - Sheriff's Association of Texas (Box 73)
  - Shepperd, John Ben (Box 73)
  - Sherman, Winthrop or Bud (Box 73)
  - Sherrill, J. N. Jr. (Box 73)
  - Sherrod, Mr. Eugene (Box 73)
  - Sherwood, Pattsie (Box 73)
  - Shifflette, Emma L. (Box 73)
  - Shipman, Raymond Richard (Box 73)
  - Shirk, Mrs. Grace (Box 73)
  - Shockley, Mr. Lorena (Box 73)
  - Shook, Mr. Clarence (Box 73)
  - Shook, Mr. D. A. (Box 73)
  - Shook, Mr. & Mrs. Jay (Box 73)
  - Shoplifting (Box 73)
  - Short, Donald E. (Box 73)
  - Short, W. N. Jr. (Box 73)
  - Sparks, Jim (Box 73)
  - Sparks, John S. (Box 73)
  - Speck, Mrs. Billie J. (Box 73)
  - Speech Pathologists (Box 73)
  - Speech Therapists (Box 73)
  - Speight, Carole A. (Box 73)
  - Speights, Betty (Box 73)
  - Spelce, Neal (Box 73)
  - Spence, Sam B. (Box 73)
  - Sperry, Bob (Box 73)
  - Sperry, Paula (Box 73)
  - Sperry & Hutchison Co. (Box 73)
  - Sperry, Mrs. Robert C. (Box 73)
  - Spiller, Michael (Box 73)
  - Spillman, Mr. Wade (Box 73)
  - Spitz, John (Box 73)
  - Spivey, Ed (Box 73)
  - Spomer, Mr. Dick (Box 73)
  - Spoonts, Mr. W. A. (Box 73)
  - Sportsmen (Box 73)
  - Spragins, Mr. & Mrs. Ed. S. Jr. (Box 73)
  - Sprague Electric Co. (Box 73)
  - Spray, James T. Jr. (Box 73)
  - Springer, Thelma (Box 73)
  - Spruiell, Mrs. Hill (Box 73)
  - Spurlock, Joe I (Box 73)
  - Spurlock, Joe C. II (Box 73)
  - Spurlock, Joe iII (Box 73)
  - Squadron Adoption program (Box 73)
  - Stages, Bill (Box 73)
  - Staley, Mr. & Mrs. Jack (Box 73)
  - Staley, Joe H. (Box 73)
  - Staley, T. C. (Box 73)
  - Stallings, Mr. John (Box 73)
  - Stambaugh, Mrs. Robert (Box 73)
  - Stanford, Bruce T.
  - Stanford, Kama (Box 73)
  - Stanely, Mr. Dan (Box 73)
  - Stanley, Pearl (Box 73)
  - Stans, Maurice (Box 73)
  - Starnes, Mrs. Elsie May (Box 73)
  - Starr, Mr. Al (Box 73)
  - State Comptroller (Box 73)
  - State Fair of Texas (Box 73)
  - State Farm Insurance Companies (Box 73)
  - State-Federal Relations (Box 73)
  - State Firemen's & Fire Marshals' Association of Texas (Box 73)
  - Stearns, Mr. Joe R. (Box 73)
  - Steed, Joe (Box 73)
  - Steinhauser, Marie (Box 73)
  - Steele, Richard P. (Box 73)
  - Steele, Tim (Box 73)
  - Steelman, Alan (Box 73)
  - Steger, Bill (Box 73)
  - Stegall, Carrie G. (Box 73)
  - Stegall, Ms. Jan (Box 73)
  - Stegall, W. E. (Box 73)
  - Steimel, Martha B. (Box 73)
  - Steimel, Walter (Box 73)
  - Steincamp, Harry (Box 73)
  - Stephen F. Austin State College (Box 73)
  - Stephen Rev. J. T. (Box 73)
  - Stephens, Mrs. Berta (Box 73)
  - Stephens, Mrs. E. V. (Box 73)
  - Stevens, Alice (Box 73)
  - Stevens, Edna Pearl (Box 73)
  - Stevens, George (Box 73)
  - Stevens, Jack (Box 73)
  - Stevens, Ramona (Box 73)
  - Stevens, Capt. Robert L. (Box 73)
  - Steward, Michael (Box 73)
  - Stewart, Sharon (Box 73)
  - Stickelman, Mr. Rick (Box 73)
  - Stiff, Anna Lucille (Box 73)
  - Stiles, Mrs. George M. (Box 73)
  - Still, Willard J. (Box 73)
  - Stilley, Frank (Francis) (Box 73)
  - Stine, Irene M. (Box 73)
  - Stinson, Mrs. Hazel L. (Box 73)
  - Stith, Mrs. R. G. (Box 73)
  - St. John, Shannon (Box 73)
  - St. Marie, Patricia (Box 73)
  - Stockard, Connie (Box 73)
  - Stockton, Dr. Gerald (Box 73)
  - Stokes, Jenny (Box 73)
  - Stokes, Ruth (Box 73)
  - Stombaugh, William K. (Box 73)
  - Stone, Roy L. (Box 73)
  - Stone, Mr. & Mrs. Sam (Box 73)
  - Stonewall, Texas (Box 73)
  - Story, James V. (Box 73)
  - Stoskus, Harry W. (Box 73)
  - Stout, A. R. (Box 73)
  - Stout, Mrs. Kay (Box 73)
  - Stowe, Mr. & Mrs. Russel Edward (Box 73)
  - Stradley, Mrs. C. W. (Box 73)
  - Strain, Mr. & Mrs. James W. (Box 73)
  - Strange, Ogden (Box 73)
  - Stratten, Brent (Box 73)
  - Stratton, Chris (Box 73)
  - Strawn, Nell (Box 73)
  - Strauss, Mr. & Mrs. Eric (Box 73)
  - Strickland, Charlie (Box 73)
  - Strickland, Mrs. G. R. (Box 73)
  - Strickland, Willie (Box 73)
  - Strong, Paul M. (Box 73)
  - Structural Pest Control Board (Box 73)
  - Stuart, Robert R. (Box 73)
  - Stubel, Miss Clara A. (Box 73)
  - Stubbs, Mrs. Raye (Box 73)
  - Studdard, Mr. & Mrs. George W. (Box 73)
  - Suber, Janice (Box 73)
  - Suggs, Mr. James C. (Box 73)
  - Sullivan, Charles (Box 73)
  - Sullivan, Delbert (Box 73)
  - Shahan, Happy (Box 74)
  - Shamrock, Texas (Box 74)
  - Shanafelt, Mrs. S. C. (Box 74)
  - Shannon, Kay (Box 74)
  - Sharkey, Donald P. (Box 74)
  - Sharp, Allen C. (Box 74)
  - Sharp, Bill (Box 74)
  - Sharp, John (Box 74)
  - Sharp, Mrs. Joy (Box 74)
  - Shapiro, David L. (Box 74)
  - Shaw, Dr. Thomas E. (Box 74)
  - Shaw, Mrs. W. D. (Box 74)
  - Shawn, Mr. & Mrs. Jesse A. (Box 74)
  - Sheffield, Ms. Patricia A. (Box 74)
  - Shell, Temple (Box 74)
  - Shelton, Mrs. Betty (Box 74)
  - Shepard, Mr. Larry (Box 74)
  - Shepherd, Ms. Sam (Box 74)
  - Sheppard, John Ben (Box 74)
  - Sheriffs Association of Texas (Box 74)
  - Sherill, Joseph N. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Sherman, Helen M. (Box 74)
  - Sherman, S. R. (Box 74)
  - Sherrill, Joseph N. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Sherwood, Mr. Lee (Box 74)
  - Sherwood, Ms. Pattsie H. (Box 74)
  - Shields, Larry (Box 74)
  - Shilling, Ms. Brenda (Box 74)
  - Shilling, Mr. Lee (Box 74)
  - Shine, Dan (Box 74)
  - Shivers, Allan (Box 74)
  - Shook, Jim (Box 74)
  - Shoen, Joe (Box 74)
  - Shop Rite Foods, Inc. (Box 74)
  - Shores, Gary H. (Box 74)
  - Don Short (Box 74)
  - Short, Rep. E. L. (Box 74)
  - Short, Ms. Helen Jane (Box 74)
  - Short, L. M. (Box 74)
  - Short, Steve (Box 74)
  - Shouse, Nancy (Box 74)
  - Shults, Mr. & Mrs. Jack (Box 74)
  - Shutters, J. D. (Box 74)
  - Siber, Ms. Bernita (Box 74)
  - Sibley, John E. (Box 74)
  - Sidlauskas, Carolyn (Box 74)
  - Siegert, Robert O. (Box 74)
  - Silber, Israel (Rabbi) (Box 74)
  - Silent Friends of Wichita Falls (Box 74)
  - Silk Gwendolyn (Box 74)
  - Sills, Mrs. Nell Sue (Box 74)
  - Silver, Warren (Box 74)
  - Simmons, Mrs. H. A. (Box 74)
  - Simmons, Jane (Box 74)
  - Simonds, E. G. (Box 74)
  - Simons, Lt. Col. Jon D. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Simmons, James (Box 74)
  - Simmons, Lloyd (Box 74)
  - Simmons, Mr. Robert (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Bill (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Bob (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Clarence (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Fred (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Mr. & Mrs. W. O. (Box 74)
  - Simpson, Mrs. W. S. (Box 74)
  - Sims, Frances (Box 74)
  - Sims, Gene (Box 74)
  - Sims, Iris (Box 74)
  - Sims, Jimmy (Box 74)
  - Sims, Mrs. Nelson (Box 74)
  - Sims, Mrs. Raymond (Box 74)
  - Sims, Steve (Box 74)
  - Sinclair, Carol (Box 74)
  - Sinclair, Ivan Earl (Box 74)
  - Sinclair, Joyce (Box 74)
  - Singletary, Ms. Katy (Box 74)
  - Sisk, Valentine (Box 74)
  - Sjolin, Mrs. Carl (Box 74)
  - Skaggs, Ms. Joyce (Box 74)
  - Skelton, Donna (Box 74)
  - Skelton, Ms. Eileen (Box 74)
  - Skelton, Mr. & Mrs. W. L. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Skinner, Ms. Darlene (Box 74)
  - Skinner, E. E. (Box 74)
  - Skinner, Smokey (Box 74)
  - Slack, Mr. & Mrs. Gowdy (Box 74)
  - Slack, Rep. Richard C. (Box 74)
  - Slay, Chester (Box 74)
  - Sledge, Larry (Box 74)
  - Slider, James L. (Box 74)
  - Sligar, James H. (Box 74)
  - Sloan, Jo Carolyn (Box 74)
  - Slusser, Ms. Ida M. (Box 74)
  - Slusser, Ms. Myrtle (Box 74)
  - Slye, William T. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Small Business (Box 74)
  - Small Business Administration (Box 74)
  - Small, Ms. Margaret j. (Box 74)
  - Small, Marvin (Box 74)
  - Small Loans (Box 74)
  - Smile (Box 74)
  - Smiley, Mrs. Judy (Box 74)
  - Smiley, Mr. & Mrs. Pat (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. Burge (Box 74)
  - Smith, Carlyle (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Carrye (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. Charles N. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Connie (Box 74)
  - Smith, Curtis W. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Danny (Box 74)
  - Smith, E. J. Jr. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Edward A. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Edward W. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. G. B. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Gordon (Box 74)
  - Smith, Gilbert (Box 74)
  - Smith, Herb (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Grady (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. Ida (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Ingrid (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. Irene (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. J. W. (Box 74)
  - Smith, James Q. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Janie (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Karen (Box 74)
  - Smith, Kenneth (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Kerri (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Kirk (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. L. F. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. Leonard B. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Leroy William (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. Lillie M. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Martha H. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Michael J. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. M. C. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Marion Frank Jr. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Dr. P. K. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Patricia (Box 74)
  - Smith, Preston (Box 74)
  - Smith, Robert S. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Ruella E. (Box 74)
  - Smith, S. Price Jr. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Sabina (Box 74)
  - Smith, Saliva (Box 74)
  - Smith, Ms. Sharon (Box 74)
  - Smith, Sidney (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mr. Stan (Box 74)
  - Smith, Terry (Box 74)
  - Smith, Mrs. Thomas W. (Box 74)
  - Smith, Vernon L. (Box 74)
  - Smoking (Box 74)
  - Smother, Clay (Box 74)
  - Snebold, Ms. Sue (Box 74)
  - Sneed, Mr. & Mrs. John H. (Box 74)
  - Snelson, Sen. Pete (Box 74)
  - Snider, Jim (Box 74)
  - Snow, Richard (Box 74)
  - Snyder, Ms. Evelyn (Box 74)
  - Snyder, Mrs. Glen (Box 74)
  - Snyder, Mr. Jerry's (Box 74)
  - Social Security (Box 74)
  - Social Services Committee (Box 74)
  - Sogard, Mr. Gail (Box 74)
  - Soil Conservation Service (Box 75)
  - Solomon, C. D. (Box 75)
  - Solar Heating (Box 75)
  - Sommerville, Ms. Zula H. (Box 75)
  - Sons of the American Revolution (Box 75)
  - Sorathia, Vali M. (Box 75)
  - Soremson, Mrs. James M. (Box 75)
  - Sosebee, Carrol Louis (Box 75)
  - Sosebee, Ms. Debbie (Box 75)
  - Sosebee, Larry A. (Box 75)
  - South Side Girls Club (Box 75)
  - South Texas (Box 75)
  - Southerland, Mr. J. D. (Box 75)
  - Southerland, Mrs. Lorna (Box 75)
  - Southern, Jo Lynn (Box 75)
  - Southern Methodist University (Box 75)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 75)
  - Southside Girls Club (Box 75)
  - Southwest Airlines (Box 75)
  - Southwest Foundation for Research & Education (Box 75)
  - Southwest Kiwanis Club (Box 75)
  - Southwest Peanut Growers Association (Box 75)
  - Southwestern Group Financial (Box 75)
  - Southwestern University (Box 75)
  - Southwest Texas Junior College (Box 75)
  - Sowards, Robert E. (Box 75)
  - Spahis, Steve (Box 75)
  - Spangler, Mrs. Elizabeth (Box 75)
  - Spangler, Ms. Myrtle D. (Box 75)
  - Sparkman, B. H. (Box 75)
  - Sparks, Connie (Box 75)
  - Spatwood, Mrs. Edna (Box 75)
  - Speakman, Ms. Mary N. (Box 75)
  - Spears, William S. (Box 75)
  - Special Olympics (Box 75)
  - Speed Limit (Box 75)
  - Speer, Mr. & Mrs. Bill (Box 75)
  - Speer, Mrs. Bill (Box 75)
  - Speer, Ms. Shirley (Box 75)
  - Speir, Col. Wilson E. (Box 75)
  - Spellings, Robert D. (Box 75)
  - Spence, R. J. (Box 75)
  - Spencer, Charles (Box 75)
  - Spencer, Tom (Box 75)
  - Spicer, Mrs. F. G. (Box 75)
  - Spikes, Lois E. (Box 75)
  - Spiller, Dr. & Mrs. Mike Jr. (Box 75)
  - Spilmans, Wade (Box 75)
  - Spivey, Broadus A. (Box 75)
  - Spongier, Mrs. Myrtle D. (Box 75)
  - Sportsmen's Club of Texas, Inc. (Box 75)
  - Spradlin, Lisa (Box 75)
  - Spragins, Ed (Box 75)
  - Spray, Mr. & Mrs. James T. (Box 75)
  - Sprinkle Systems (Box 75)
  - Sprinkles, Henry (Box 75)
  - Sprowls, Mrs. Hubert (Box 75)
  - Spurlock, B. W. (Box 75)
  - Spurlock, Joe II (Box 75)
  - Sraw, Abdul Rehman (Box 75)
  - St. Mary's University (Box 75)
  - Staber, Ms. Sue (Box 75)
  - Stacks, Mrs. Bess (Box 75)
  - Stacy, Mr. & Mrs. Wayman (Box 75)
  - Stafford, Mr. W. R. (Box 75)
  - Staley, Conrad (Box 75)
  - Stallcup, Morris (Box 75)
  - Stanley, Ms. Leola (Box 75)
  - Stark, Morris (Box 75)
  - Starnes, B. L. (Box 75)
  - Starnes, Ms. Elsie M. (Box 75)
  - Starnes, Ms. Linda (Box 75)
  - Starnes, M. (Box 75)
  - Starnes, Mr. Robby (Box 75)
  - State Association of the Justices of the Peace & Constables (Box 75)
  - State Auditor (Box 75)
  - State Bar of Texas (Box 75)
  - State Board of Bar Examiners (Box 75)
  - State Board of Law Examiners (Box 75)
  - State Capitol (Box 75)
  - State Employees (Box 75)
  - State Firemen's & Firemarshalls' Association (Box 75)
  - State Law Enforcement Association (Box 75)
  - Staton, Lester (Box 75)
  - Stearns, Mrs. Joe R. (Box 75)
  - Stearns, William L. (Box 75)
  - Steed, Mr. Netum A. (Box 75)
  - Steele, Jonathan Michael (Box 75)
  - Steimel, Walter L. (Box 75)
  - Steincamp, Mr. & Mrs. Harry E. (Box 75)
  - Stenholm, Charles W. (Box 75)
  - Stephens, Jean (Box 75)
  - Stephens, Lorene (Box 75)
  - Stephens, Paul (Box 75)
  - Stephen F. Austin State University (Box 75)
  - Stephens, Pam (Box 75)
  - Stephenson, Dr. Philip L. (Box 75)
  - Sterley, Mr. & Mrs. George A. (Box 75)
  - Sterley, George A. (Box 75)
  - Sterley, Mrs. Nancy (Box 75)
  - Sterling, Miss Jan (Box 75)
  - Stevens, Dr. Irma Ned (Box 75)
  - Stevens, Mrs. Jan (Box 75)
  - Stevenson, David M. (Box 75)
  - Stevenson, Floyd (Box 75)
  - Steward, Mae (Box 75)
  - Steward, Stephen (Box 75)
  - Stewart, Ms. Betty N. (Box 75)
  - Stewart, Ms. Flora (Box 75)
  - Stewart, Mrs. H. K. (Box 75)
  - Stewart, James H. Jr. (Box 75)
  - Stewart Margaret (Box 75)
  - Stephens, Mrs. M. (Box 75)
  - Stiglets, Mr. T. Dwight (Box 75)
  - Stiles, Ms. Georgia (Box 75)
  - Still, Mr. Willard J. (Box 75)
  - Still, Mr. & Mrs. Wilmer E. (Box 75)
  - Stilley, Ms. Ruth (Box 75)
  - Stillson, Dr. William T. (Box 75)
  - Stimpson, Ms. Eula Mae (Box 75)
  - Stirman, Mrs. E. C. (Box 75)
  - Stirman, Mr. & Mrs. P. W. "Tex" (Box 75)
  - Stockard, Mrs. J. D. (Box 75)
  - Stockton, Gerald (Box 75)
  - Stockwell, Mrs. Kathy (Box 75)
  - Stogner, Ms. Linda J. (Box 75)
  - Stokes, Mrs. Ruth (Box 75)
  - Stone, Clota O. (Box 75)
  - Stone, Mrs. Maxine (Box 75)
  - Stone, Roy Lee (Box 75)
  - Stone, Mrs. Roy (Box 75)
  - Stone, Sam (Box 75)
  - Stoneking, Mr. & Mrs. George (Box 75)
  - Story, Edward C. (Box 75)
  - Stout, Rev. David (Box 75)
  - Stout, Don W. (Box 75)
  - Stovall, Ms. Peggy (Box 75)
  - Strain, Mrs. J. W. (Box 75)
  - Strake, George W. Jr. (Box 75)
  - Stratten, Cecil (Box 75)
  - Strayhorn, Christopher Ward (Box 75)
  - Street, Mr. J. C. (Box 75)
  - Streich, Mr. & Mrs. Cecil (Box 75)
  - Strickland, C. D. (Box 75)
  - Stricklkand, Osborne W. (Box 75)
  - Strip Mining (Box 75)
  - Stringer, Mr. Tom (Box 75)
  - Stromer, Mr. & Mrs. Bill (Box 75)
  - Strubel, Ms. Clara (Box 75)
  - Stubb, C. O. (Box 75)
  - Stubbeman, David (Box 75)
  - Sturgeon, Ms. Dianne (Box 75)
  - Sul Ross State University (Box 75)
  - Sullenberger, Ms. Sandra (Box 75)
  - Sullivan, Berry (Box 75)
  - John Sullivan (Box 75)
  - Sullivan, Mr. & Mrs. W. E. (Box 75)
  - Sullivant, Bill (Box 75)
  - Summers, T. Keith (Box 75)
  - Sun Day (Box 75)
  - Sund, Ms. Eldon H. (Box 75)
  - Sunday Closing Law (Box 75)
  - Sunset Commission (Box 75)
  - Sunset Law (Box 75)
  - Superport (Box 75)
  - Surgikos (Box 75)
  - Surles, Ralph (Box 75)
  - Surveyors (Box 75)
  - Sutherland, Steve (Box 75)
  - Sutton, Mr. & Mrs. G. J. (Box 75)
  - Sutton, Lou Nelle (Box 75)
  - Sutton, Dr. R. N. (Box 75)
  - Sutton, Robert (Box 75)
  - Swafford, Emma (Box 75)
  - Swanner, Ms. Elizabeth J. (Box 75)
  - Swanson, Mrs. O. L. (Box 75)
  - Swagerty, Mr. & Mrs. Perrall (Box 75)
  - Sweeney, M. Gayle (Box 75)
  - Swenson, Gary (Box 75)
  - Swint, W. B. (Box 75)
  - Sykes, Mrs. Shirley (Box 75)
  - Syron, Ms. Susan (Box 75)
  - Syrus, Vickie (Box 75)
  - Szymanski, Mrs. Linda (Box 75)
  - Taber, Herbert L. (Box 76)
  - Tackett, J. Derwood (Box 76)
  - Tackitt, Mrs. Velma M. (Box 76)
  - TACT (Box 76)
  - Taliaferro, Frand (Box 76)
  - Talley, James A. (Box 76)
  - Talley, Mr. Jimmy L. (Box 76)
  - Tanner, Grace A. (Box 76)
  - Tanner, Mr. & Mrs. Simon M. (Box 76)
  - Taras, Miss Tarasue (Box 76)
  - Tarbox, Elmer (Box 76)
  - Tarkington, Mr. & Mrs. Wayne (Box 76)
  - Tarleton State University (Box 76)
  - Tarrant County (Box 76)
  - Tate, David (Box 76)
  - Tate, Mr. & Mrs. E. A. (Box 76)
  - Tate, Mrs. Howard (Box 76)
  - Tate, J. C. (Box 76)
  - Tate, Linda (Box 76)
  - Tate, Ms. Teri (Box 76)
  - Tatom, Mrs. Myrtle (Box 76)
  - Tatum, Mr. E. J. (Box 76)
  - Tatum, Ms. Jeanette (Box 76)
  - Tax Assessors (Box 76)
  - Tax Assessors & Collectors Association of Texas (Box 76)
  - Takacs, Mr. M. (Box 76)
  - Tanner, Bettye (Box 76)
  - Tanner, Monnie (Box 76)
  - Tanner, Perry Jr. (Box 76)
  - Taras, Suzanne (Box 76)
  - Tarleton State College (Box 76)
  - Tarry Moving & Storage Co. (Box 76)
  - Tate, Dr. Willis (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Bobby (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Christene (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Doris (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Eldon (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Col. & Mrs. Floyd (Box 76)
  - Taylor, George (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Gladys (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Mr. & Mrs. H. L. (Box 76)
  - Taylor, J. Richard W. (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Treba (Box 76)
  - Taylor, J. Wesley B. (Box 76)
  - Taylor, James I. D.D.S. (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Jerry Dale (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Mr. Marion N. (Box 76)
  - Taylor, Ola Mae (Box 76)
  - Tax-Assessor-Collector, Wichita County, Texas (Box 76)
  - Taxes-Oil (Box 76)
  - Taxation File 1 (Box 76)
  - Taxation File 2 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1973 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1974 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1975 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1976 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1977 (Box 76)
  - Taxation 1978 (Box 76)
  - Texas Committee of Organizations for the Handicapped (Box 77)
  - Texas Conference of Churches (Box 77)
  - Texas Congress of Parents & Teachers (Box 77)
  - Texas Conservation Council (Box 77)
  - Texas Consumer Association (Box 77)
  - Texas County Agricultural Agents Association (Box 77)
  - Texas County Judges & Commisoners Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Cowboy Artists' Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Criminal Defense Lawyers Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Dental Laboratory Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Department of Community Affairs (Box 77)
  - State Department of Public Welfare (Box 77)
  - Texas District & County Attorneys Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Educational Secretaries Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Educators Political Action Council
  - Texas Elementary Principals & Supervisors Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Employers' Insurance Association (Box 77)
  - Texas Employment Commission (Box 77)
  - Texas Environmental Coalition (Box 77)
  - Texas Farm Bureau (Box 77)
  - Texas Farm Bureau Insurance Companies (Box 77)
  - Texas Farmers Union (Box 77)